- Hey. - Hi.
-嘿  -嘿
Pheebs, what's wrong?
菲比  出了什么事吗
I'm just so exhausted from dragging around
戴着这个超大订婚戒指
this huge engagement ring.
快要把我累死了
Oh, my God.
噢  天啊
Congratulations.
恭喜
So did he get on one knee?
他有没有跪下来
Did he have a speech prepared?
他有准备求婚词吗
Oh, did he cry?
噢  他有哭吗
Yeah, big surprise, I like proposals.
没错  我喜欢求婚  很奇怪吗
Well, it was really sweet,
实在是很温馨
and, like, the most romantic thing ever.
是我人生中最浪漫的一刻
Here's to Phoebe,
嘿  我们来敬菲比
who's found the greatest guy in the world.
为了她找到世界上最好的男人干一杯
To Phoebe and--
敬菲比和...
I want to say "Mike"?
应该是迈克吧
To Phoebe and Mike.
敬菲比和迈克
Thank you.
谢谢大家
Oh, and I have something for you.
对了  我有点东西要给你
It's my little black book.
这是我的小黑本本
It's got the numbers of all the guys I've dated.
里面有我约会过所有男生的电话
Oh, Phoebe, that's nice,
噢  菲比  很谢谢你
but you know what? I think I'm okay.
但我想我用不上了
Why don't you just give it
你还是把它送给你
to one of your other single girlfriends.
其他独身的女性朋友吧
I would, but you're the last one.
我也想  但你是最后一个独身的了
Give me the book!
那给我吧
"Pablo Diaz.
巴布罗·迪亚斯
Brady Smith.
布里迪·史密斯
Guy in Van"?
"开货车的男生"
Oh, my first love.
那是我的初恋
What is the red X next to
巴伯·格里莫的名字旁边
Bob Gremore's name mean?
标着个红叉是什么意思
Dead.
挂了
Oh, it's okay. No, he was old. Yeah.
没关系  他已经很老了
And he lived a full life.
他经历相当丰富
He was in the first wave at Omaha Beach.
奥马哈登陆  他第一波上去的
oh, I'm sorry. I should've given you guys my black book
嘿  对不起  我结婚时也应该
when I got married.
把我的电话本给你们男生的
Although, it wasn't so much a book
尽管那不算是电话本
as a napkin.
只是一张皱皱的纸...
With Janice's phone number on it.
...上面写着珍妮斯的电话
Phoebe, isn't Jethro Tull a band?
菲比  杰思罗·塔尔不是一个乐队吗
Oh, yes, they are.
没错
《老友记》第十季第六集 罗斯的科研补助金
《老友记》  第十季  第6集 罗斯的科研补助金
Hey, honey.
嘿  老婆
Hey, sweetie.
嘿  老公
- Is Monica not here? - No.
-莫尼卡不在吗  -不在
Then I'll tell you.
那我先告诉你吧
My agency was bidding for a big account, and they got it.
我们公司中标了一个大广告订单
It's my first national commercial.
这是我第一个跨国广告
Cool.
酷
And I don't want to brag,
不是我吹牛
but a lot of the ideas were mine.
但很多内容都是我构思出来的
Hell, you weren't there.
去他的  你又没在那
All the ideas were mine.
全部构思都是我的
That's great.
太好了
Hey, can you cast me in it?
嘿  可以介绍我去拍广告吗
I really don't think you're right for the part.
...不知道啊  我想你不适合里面的角色
What do you mean? I can do anything.
怎么会  我可以演任何角色
I'm a chameleon.
我是一条变色龙呢
I'm old.
我很老
I'm tired.
我很累
Oh, I am hot. I'm cold.
嘿  我很热  我很冷
Come on, what can't I do?
拜托  有什么我不能演
First of all, bravo.
我得说  精彩...
But I don't think you're right for this.
但我觉得你真的不适合
The part's a stuffy college professor.
这个角色是一个死板的大学教授
I can do that.
也可以啊
Hello, I'm your professor.
你好  我是你们的教授
When I'm not busy thinking of important things,
当我停下来没想重要事情的时候...
or professing...
或者没在教授的时候...
...l like to use-- What's the product?
我会用...  噢  是什么产品
Software that facilitates inter-business networking e-solutions.
电子商务网络解决方案
I'm cold.
我很冷
- Hey. - Hey.
-嘿  -嘿
Guess who's a finalist
猜猜谁有可能得到
for a huge research grant?
一笔庞大的科研补助金
I'll give you a hint.
给你个提示
He's looking right at you.
他正在看着你
Well, unless it's the creepy guy
除非你说的是
with his hand up his kilt...
那个把手伸入他裙子的怪人
...I'm gonna say, "Congratulations."
我要说  恭喜你
I'm so excited.
我实在是太兴奋了
Apparently, I beat out hundreds of other applicants...
我击败了其他的几百个竞争者
...including five guys I went to graduate school with.
包括我上研究生时的五个同学
Not that I'm keeping score, or anything. Five.
不是我吹嘘  但...五个人
- Wow, that's great. - Yeah.
-哇  太厉害了  -是啊
So tell me about the grant.
那个是什么补助金
Well, okay, it's for $25,000.
那是两万五千元的资金
And if I get it,
如果我得到了
I'll be able to complete my field research.
那我就可以完成我那领域的研究了
And there will be an article about me
然后我就可以在《古生物学刊》里
in the Paleontology Review.
发表我的论文了
It'll be the first time my name is in there...
那将会是我头一次在那本书上发表论文
...without people raising serious questions about my work.
而其他人就不会怀疑我的研究了
Are you talking about the Dewer Grant?
等等  你是说杜瓦补助金
Yeah. Why?
没错  怎么了
Benjamin Hobart is administering that grant.
本杰明·哈伯特管理着那个补助金
- Your ex-boyfriend? - Yeah.
-你的前任男朋友  -对
So your ex-boyfriend is gonna determine
那么说  你的前男友决定了
if your new boyfriend gets this grant?
你现任男友是否能得到那笔钱
Wow, your new boyfriend is screwed.
你的现任男友完蛋了
No. No, we ended on great terms.
没有  我们很愉快地分手
I mean if anything,
我意思是  如果对此事有影响的话
I think this could help you. You know what?
那也肯定是帮助你的
Why don't we all go out to dinner,
我们可以把他约出来吃个饭啊
and I can introduce you.
我可以把你介绍给他
If you think it'd help.
是吗  你觉得有帮助吗
Yeah, absolutely. I'll call him.
当然啦  我给他打电话啦
Now, is there anything I could do to butter him up?
我可以做什么去...迎合他啊
Anything he really likes?
他有什么嗜好
He does have a pretty serious latex fetish.
他确实有严重的乳胶恋物情结
We'll see how dinner goes.
还是看看晚饭会怎么样吧
- Hey. - Hey, you want to go see a movie?
-嘿  -嘿  想去看电影吗
I told you I had to spend all day clearing out stuff
我已经告诉过你我今天一整天要打扫
so Mike could move in.
好让迈克搬进来住
- Oh, right. - Yeah.
-噢  对哦  -没错.
Now that I'm here,
既然我都来了
I might as well help with the cleaning and organizing.
我就帮你清洁和收拾一下吧
I just happen to have my label maker.
刚好我还带了打标签机
Oh, it's so hard to get rid of stuff.
要丢弃自己的物品太难了
Did you and Chandler make compromises
你和钱德勒要同居的时候
when you moved in together?
有为丢弃东西妥协过吗
Chandler did.
钱德勒有
What does he want you to give up?
他想你丢弃什么
A bunch of stuff.
很多东西啊
And the worst one,
我最舍不得的是...
he wants me to get rid of Gladys.
他要我丢掉格拉达斯
Who's Gladys?
谁是格拉达斯
What a tragic loss.
多么可怕的损失
Yeah, I really hate to give her up.
就是说  我真的不想放弃她啊
Oh, I know. Oh, you should take her.
噢  我想到了  你可以带她走啊
I don't know.
这样...不好吧...
What, you don't like her?
为什么  你不喜欢她吗
Of course I do. What's not to like?
我当然喜欢她啊  有什么好不喜欢的呢
I'd take her in a minute.
我恨不得马上就把她拿走
But I think that you're giving up too easy.
但我觉得你现在说放弃太早了
Honey, I think that you need to fight for her.
我想你应该为她而斗争
- Really, you think? - Absolutely.
-真的  你这么觉得  -当然啦
You say to him,
你对他说
"I'm sorry, Mike, I can't live without her.
对不起  迈克  没有她我就活不了
She means too much to me."
她对我来说太重要了
Okay, I'll fight for her. Okay.
好的  我是该为她争取一下
Oh, wait. I just realized, if I do that,
等等  我忽然想到...  如果我这样做
that means you don't get her.
你就无法得到她了
Damn it, I did not think this through.
可恶  我怎么没想到呢
- Hey, guys. - Hey.
-嘿  你们  -嘿
Oh, any word on casting yet?
你给我的推荐有回复了吗
I told you, you're not right for the part.
乔伊  我已经说过了  你不适合那个角色
What do you mean?
什么意思啊
Rach, don't I seem like a professor
瑞秋  你会不会花钱
you'd buy some kind of e-crap from?
买像我这样的教授介绍的电子货啊
I'm sorry,
不好意思
this sounds like something I'm never gonna be interested in.
你说的东西估计我这辈子也不会感兴趣
Look, come on, please?
拜托啦
It's not like I'm asking you for some crazy favor.
又不是要诚心为难你
This is what I do for a living.
我就是干这行的啊
I am a professional actor.
我是个职业的演员呢
Man, I'm two hours late for work.
迟到了两小时了
Here's a copy of my reel.
这里有我的一盘磁带
It's got all the commercials that I've been in.
里面有我拍过的所有广告
- Joe-- - Just watch it.
-乔伊...  -你就看一下吧
If you don't like it,
如果你不喜欢
don't pass it on to your bosses.
就别给你上司就是了
- Fine. - Thank you.
-好吧  -谢谢
- Work, Joe. - Damn it.
-工作啦  乔伊  -可恶
What am I gonna do now?
我该怎么办啦
Just pass the tape along.
就给你上司看看咯
He's not right for the part.
他的确不适合演这个
If I suggest him,
如果我推荐他
my bosses will think I'm an idiot.
我的老板会觉得我是个白痴
And that's something they should learn on their own.
我希望我的老板能迟些才发现这一点
Just tell Joey that you watched the tape...
那就告诉乔伊你看过带子
...and you liked it, but your bosses didn't.
你很喜欢  但你的老板们不喜欢
Then that way, you're the good guy,
那样  你就成了好人
and they're the bad guy.
坏人就是你的老板啦
That's good. I liked it, they didn't.
好主意  我喜欢  老板不喜欢
Joey, for God's sake, go to work.
乔伊  看在上帝份上  去工作啦
I can't believe I'm about to meet Benjamin Hobart.
真不敢相信我马上就要见到本杰明·哈伯特
I've always thought of him as someone I'd invite...
我一直以为
...to my fantasy dinner party.
只有在梦中才能和他共聚晚餐呢
Do you think there's any chance
他会不会带上一些
he'll bring Christie Brinkley or C-3PO?
他喜欢的小玩偶来呢
Sorry, it looks like it's just him.
对不起  看来他是自己来的
Charlie.
查莉
My God, you look absolutely stunning.
天啊  你简直太美了
Well, I am having a good hair day.
是吗  今天我特地去了理发
- It's so good to see you. - Oh, you too.
-见到你真好  -我也是
I'm okay.
我没事
I'm sorry. Ross Geller, Benjamin Hobart.
对不起...罗斯·盖勒  本杰明·哈伯特
It's an honor to meet you.
很荣幸见到你
I can't tell you how long...
我仰慕你都不知道多久了
...I've been an admirer of your work. I mean, that Nobel Prize.
我是说  你得了诺贝尔奖  喔...
I mean, I have to tell you
不得不对你说
that you're one of the reasons I got into the field.
你是我进入这个领域原因之一
Well, likewise.
是吗  我也久仰大名
Actually not likewise.
其实没有久仰
I'd never heard of you until this morning.
我今早才第一次听到你的名字
But it's nice to be nice.
但为人随和没什么不好
- Shall we? - Yeah. Thank you.
-我们坐  -好的  谢谢
I can't believe that you chose this restaurant.
不敢相信你选了这个餐馆
Do you remember the night?
你还记得那天晚上吗
Oh, my God. I completely forgot.
噢天啊  我完全忘记了
Oh, my God, I can't believe they let us back in this place.
天啊  真不敢相信他们能让我们进门
You weren't there.
你当时不在场
No, but, you know, it's just a funny image.
是不在  但想想都好笑
You know, the two of you in this restaurant with the....
想想你们两个  在这个餐馆  还...
Ross, why don't you tell Benji
罗斯  我去洗手间的时候
about your proposal while I go to the ladies' room.
你跟本杰说说你的方案吧
So tell me about it.
来吧  告诉我吧
Painted Desert:在亚利桑那州北部
我们会在彩色沙漠里进行挖掘
There are still several areas that haven't been fully excavated.
因为里面有些地区还没完全挖掘
- Break up with Charlie. - What?
-和查莉分手吧  -什么
What?
什么
Did you just say, "Break up with Charlie"?
你刚才说  "和查莉分手"吗
Well, yes and no.
可以说是  也可以说不是
Yes, I did say it. And no, I didn't not say it.
是  我是这样说了  不是的话就是说我没有不说
Kind of inappropriate, don't you think?
你不觉得这么说有点不妥吗
Listen, I'm sorry.
对不起
I just haven't seen her for so long,
因为我太久没有见她了
all these feelings are rushing back.
以前的感觉又涌上心头
I'm starting to realize
让我意识到
how much I've missed her.
我有多想念她
And I'm gonna need you to break up with her.
我需要你和她分手
Are you serious?
你是说真的吗
If you say, yes, then I'm serious.
如果你说行  那我就是认真的
If you say, no, then I'm joking.
如果你说不行  那我就是开玩笑
- No. - Joking it is.
-不行  -我开玩笑的
Hi, sorry I'm late.
嗨  对不起  我迟到了
Hey, how'd it go with Mike?
嘿  和迈克谈得怎样
Is he gonna let you keep the painting?
他肯让你保留那幅画吗
No, he really hates it.
不行  他实在很讨厌它
But he's gonna let me keep my box of human hair.
但他肯让我留下我那盒头发
So you gotta pick your battles.
所以我只能妥协了
But the good news is, Gladys is yours.
但好消息是  格拉达斯已经属于你了
Wow, what's the bad news?
那坏消息呢
Who's Gladys?
谁是格拉达斯
Oh, she's that work of art I made.
她是我的手工作品
You know, with the woman coming out of the frame.
就是女人从相框里出来的那幅
And Monica gets to keep her?
给莫尼卡了吗
In her house? I am so jealous.
放在她房间里  羡慕嫉妒恨啊
I didn't know you wanted her too.
我不知道你也想要她啊
Well, I mean, sure, of course.
我...当然想要啊
But you already gave that to Monica, so....
但...你已经给了莫尼卡了  所以...
You know, I would give her up for you.
为了你  我可以放弃她
No, I couldn't let you do that.
不行  我不可以让你这样做的
- No, but I want to. - But I don't want you to.
-但我想这样做  -但我不想你这样做
- But I insist. - But I insist harder.
-但我坚持  -但我更坚持
Girls. Girls. Stop. Okay, we'll flip a coin.
女生们  停一停好吗  我们投硬币决定吧
Heads, she's Rachel's.
正面  她是瑞秋的
Tails, she's Monica's.
反面  她就是莫尼卡的
Tails. Monica, she's yours.
反面  莫尼卡  她是你的了
No, that landed in your food.
不行  它掉到你的食物里了
No, no, that's okay.
不  没关系
You won fair and square. I'm so sad.
你赢得光明正大  我太难过了
Hey, Joe?
嘿  乔伊
- What's up? - Bad news.
-什么事  -坏消息
I watched the tape
我看过了带子
and passed it along to my bosses
并把它交给我的老板们
and they weren't interested.
但他们不感兴趣
I'm sorry, man.
对不起  老兄
But you watched the tape?
但...你看过这带子吗
Yeah, I liked it.
是啊  我...我很喜欢啊
But my bosses didn't go for it.
但...我的老板不喜欢
Stupid sons of bitches.
这些愚蠢的狗杂种
You didn't watch the tape.
你没有看过这带子
What? Of course I did.
什么  我当然看啦
Look, it's one thing not to cast me,
你不推荐我是一回事
but to lie to me?
但你对我说谎
I'm not lying to you. I watched it.
我没有说谎啊  我看了啦
You lied again.
你看  又说谎
- I watched it. - Keep going, Pinocchio.
-我看了  -继续说谎吧  匹诺曹
- I did. - No, you didn't.
-我看了  -没有  你没看
I'm telling you, I watched the tape.
我告诉你  我看了这带子
- Did you watch the tape? - No.
-你看过这带子吗  -没有
All right. The selection committee has chosen
评选委员会选出
the three of you as our finalists.
你们三人于今天作最后评核
The ultimate decision will be based on the answers
最终决定会基于
you give to the questions I ask.
你们如何回答我的问题
We're gonna go ahead and start with Dr. Li.
先从李博士开始吧
Dr. Li, you claim the field is too reliant
李博士  你提出学界
on the Linnaean taxonomic system.
太依赖林奈分类系统
How do you propose to correct this problem?
那你打算怎么解决这个问题
Well, I believe that the answers
我相信解决办法
lie in the osteological evidence.
在骨骼证据上
- I plan to begin there. - Interesting.
-我打算从那里入手  -很有趣
I guess.
是吧
Dr. Biely, your proposal includes some fieldwork.
白莉博士  你的方案有一些挖掘工作
Where might that take place?
你会选择哪里
Primarily in the Pierre Shale region of South Dakota.
首先是南达科他州的皮尔页岩地区
Certainly. Very well.
当然  很好
And Dr.Geller, when is my birthday?
那盖勒博士  我生日是什么时候
What? I--
什么  我...
Care to venture a guess?
不能猜一下吗
- May 12? - That's not even kind of close.
-5月12号  -还差很远呢
Dr. Li, how many graduate students you'd be needing?
李博士  你需要多少个研究生呢
Half a dozen.
六个
I see. And Dr. Biely?
明白了  那白莉博士呢
Three for excavation, and two for analysis.
三个负责挖掘  两个负责分析
Certainly. Dr. Geller, which 1965 Shirelles hit...
当然  盖勒博士  1965年沙伦斯乐队
...was later covered by a popular British Invasion band?
被哪支英国乐队盖过风头
What? I need six graduate students.
什么...  我需要六个研究生
No, I'm sorry.
不是  对不起
We were looking for "Baby It's You."
答案是  "宝贝  就是你"
"Baby It's You."
"宝贝  就是你"
What? Wait just a minute.
什么...  等等  等一下
None of my questions have anything to do with paleontology.
我的问题没有一条是关于古生物学的
You're right, I apologize.
没错  我该道歉
Scratch the last question.
那最后一条问题
Spell "Boscodictiasaur."
拼写单词"Boscodictiasaur"
I've never heard of a "Boscodictiasaur."
我没有听过这个单词啊
Yeah, I just made it up. Spell it.
是  我乱编的单词  快拼
Okay. B-O-S-
好的  B...O...S...
No, it starts with a silent M.
不  开头有个不发音的"M"
Oh, come on!
拜托
I can't believe Joey.
我不敢相信乔伊这么说我
I hate being called a liar.
我讨厌被人称为骗子
But you are a liar.
但你就是个骗子
What did I just say?
我刚刚怎么说的
Are you still here?
你还在啊
Yes. And I have to say.
是的  而且我不得不说
And I'm not just hurt, I'm insulted.
我不仅仅是受伤害  我感觉被侮辱了一样
When I tell somebody I did something--
当我说我已经做了某事...
Okay, hold on, let me just stop you right there, okay?
好了好了...  我打断你一下好吗
First, you lied. Right?
首先  你说谎  对吗
Then you lied about lying, okay?
然后  你又说谎去圆谎  好吗
Then you lied about
然后  你又再说谎
lying about lying, okay?
去圆你刚才圆的谎
So before you lie about
所以在你说谎去圆你刚才
lying about lying about lying about lying....
为圆谎...而说的谎...的那个谎言...
Stop lying.
不要说谎啦
Why are you so sure
为什么你这么肯定
I didn't watch this tape?
我没有看过那带子
You wanna know why?
你想知道...
Well, this is going well.
事情发展得不错呢
Here's how I know you didn't watch.
这就是我知道你没看的原因了
If you had seen what was on this tape,
如果你看了这带子
believe me, you'd have some comments.
你绝对不会没有话说的
All right, remember, I got paid a lot of money for this...
听好  我收了很多钱才去拍这个广告
...and it only aired in Japan.
而且只在日本地区放映
Ichiban.
一级棒
Ichiban, lipstick for men.
一级棒  男用唇膏
And that's how I know you didn't watch the tape.
这就是我知道你没看的原因
He really is a chameleon.
他真的是一条变色龙呢
Well, Gladys, say hello to your new home.
格拉达斯  跟你的新家打个招呼吧
- Oh, my. - Wow.
-我的... -哇
Oh, she is so nice and big.
她真漂亮  又显眼
Oh, Monica, where are you going to display Gladys,
莫尼卡  你会把她放到什么地方
oh, so proudly?
你得多骄傲啊
I haven't really settled on a spot yet.
我还没决定放在哪里
How about right above the TV?
那不如放在电视机上面吧
That way, it will be the first thing that you see
这样的话  人们一进门
when you walk in the door.
就马上看得到了
Yeah, yeah,
好啊  好啊
and you can get rid of that French poster.
那你就可以丢掉那法国的海报了
- I like that poster. - Really?
-我喜欢那海报啊  -是吗
It doesn't have anything coming out of it.
它没有东西可以"冒"出来啊
Or maybe there's someplace for her in your bedroom?
又或者你的卧室里有空位吗
There's nothing above your bed.
噢  你床头还空着呢
Are you still here?
你怎么还在这
Oh, hi. Hello.
噢  嗨  你好
Have you come to ask me some more paleontology-related questions?
你是来问我古生物学的问题的吗
Your grandmother's nickname, perhaps?
可能你要问我你祖母的昵称吧
Aunt Margaret's pants size?
还是你马格莉特阿姨内裤的尺寸
I've come here to apologize.
我是来道歉的
I think I may have let my feelings...
我想我对查莉的感情…
...for Charlie interfere with the interview process.
影响到面试的程序了
No. Stop.
没有  哪里有
Anyway, I decided to offer you the grant.
不管怎么说  我决定把资金批给你
Really?
真的吗
There is just one small stipulation.
只是还有一个条件
I have to break up with Charlie?
我要和查莉分手
Hey, you got one right.
嘿  你终于答对一次了
You're crazy.
你发神经
Crazy or romantic?
神经  还是...浪漫
Crazy.
神经
- Or? - Get out!
-还是...  -出去
Oh, my God.
噢  天啊
What?
什么
Joey, what is this thing doing here?
乔伊  这东西在这里干嘛
I got her from Monica.
我在莫尼卡那里拿过来的
She sold it to me for a very reasonable price.
她出了个很合理的价格
Joey, we're not keeping this.
乔伊  我们不能留着这个
But it's an original Buffay.
但它是原版的布菲作品啊...
All right, fine. You can keep it.
好的  没关系  你就留着吧
As long as you don't mind that she's haunted.
只要你不介意她有灵魂附体
Hey, what? What?
嘿  什么...
Well, legend has it, Joey,
有这样一个传说  乔伊
that she comes alive when you're asleep.
她在你半夜睡觉的时候会活过来
She climbs out of the frame...
她爬出这画框
...and then drags her half-a-body
然后她拖着她这半个身体
across the floor...
爬在地板上
...just looking for legs to steal.
想办法去偷一双腿
And then with her one good hand...
然后她用她唯一的一只手
...she slowly reaches up...
慢慢地...
...and turns your doorknob.
扭开门把手
Get that legless witch out of here!
拿走这没脚的妖怪
Hey, I sold that to Joey.
嘿  我把它卖给乔伊了
Yeah, well, I told him it's haunted.
所以我骗他这是鬼怪了
Two can play at this game.
我们都会玩这种把戏
Too late. You can't give it back.
不行  太迟了  你不能退货
Oh, yes, I can.
我当然可以
No, you can't, she's yours.
不  你不可以  她是你的
- She's yours. - She's yours.
-她是你的  -是你的
She's yours.
她是你的
Hey.
嘿
- She's mine. - She's mine.
-她是我的  -是我的
You guys, you don't have to fight over her anymore.
你们啊  不用为她争吵了
Whoever doesn't get Gladys,
谁得不到格拉达斯
gets Glynnis.
就把格林妮斯拿回去吧
- I want Gladys. - She's mine.
-我要格拉达斯  -她是我的
- She's mine. - She's mine.
-她是我的  -她是我的
I know. Look, I'm sorry I didn't give them your tape.
很抱歉我没有把你的带子给他们
And I promise next time to submit you,
我保证  下次无论合不合适
whether I think you're right or not.
我都会把你推荐上去的
That's not the point, Chandler.
重点不是这个啊  钱德勒
The point is that you lied.
重点是  你说了谎
I know. You're right.
我知道  你说的对
What's it gonna take for you to forgive me?
我要做什么你才能原谅我
Oh, my God.
噢  天啊
Excellent.
绝了
Now what do you say?
现在你该说什么
Lying is wrong.
说谎是不对的
And? And?
还有呢...  还有呢...
I'm a pretty little girl.
我是个漂亮美眉
I knew it.
我早就知道啦
Your ex-boyfriend is insane.
你的前男友是个疯子
Did you get the grant?
随便啦  你得到那笔资金了吗
No. And you wanna know why?
没有  你想知道为什么吗
Because your ex-boyfriend is still in love with you.
因为你的前男友还是爱着你
- What? - Yeah.
-什么  -没错
He wouldn't give me the grant,
他没有给我那笔补助
because I wouldn't give you up.
就因为我没有放弃你
Benji isn't in love with me.
本杰不会还爱着我的
I mean, he broke up with me.
因为当时是他抛弃我
And besides, he's a very ethical man.
而且  他是个很有道德的人
Really?
是吗
Is it ethical to ask someone in a grant review:
在面谈中问这种问题
"Who was the voice of Underdog?"
《超狗任务》中谁给狗配音
I'm sure he was just joking, Ross.
我肯定他是在开玩笑  罗斯
If you don't believe me, let's go talk to him.
如果你不相信我  我们去找他对质吧
I'm telling you,
可以告诉你
he didn't ask me one paleontological question.
他没有问过我一个关于考古学的问题
Seriously?
真的吗
Oh, I'm sorry. No, he did ask me one:
哦  不是  他问了我一个
"How do you spell Boscodictiasaur?"
怎么拼"boscodictiosaur"
Well, if it's like the Lake Mbosco in Congo,
和刚果的巴斯克湖拼法一样
then M-B-O--
那是M...B...O...
Damn it.
可恶
Dr. Geller. Charlie, what are you doing here?
盖勒博士...  查莉  你们到这来干什么
I want you to tell her everything.
我要你告诉他一切
About the deal you tried to make with me,
告诉他你想和我做的交易
about the crazy questions you--
那些神经病的问题
Wally Cox. That's the voice of Underdog.
沃利·考克斯  他就是《超狗任务》的配音
Like I tried to tell you in the interview...
就如之前的调查我告诉你一样
...this grant is not based on
这笔资金不是为了
your knowledge of pretty useless trivia.
这些无聊的知识而设的
No, don't do that.
不  不  不  别这样
I want you to look her in the eyes
我要你看着她的眼睛
and tell her the truth.
告诉她真相
Benji?
本杰
All right. It's true.
是的  的确是这样
I behaved horribly,
我之前简直是乱来
but it's only because I still love you.
但这都是因为我还爱着你
And I would do anything
只要你回到我身边
to have you back in my life.
我可以做任何事
Too little, too late, Benji.
早干嘛去了  本杰
I can't believe this.
我不敢相信
I never should've broken up with you.
我真不应该离开你
I think about you all the time.
我无时无刻不在想你
Do you ever still think about me?
难道你就从来没想过我吗
No.
没有
- Yes. - What?
-有  -什么
I don't know what to say, Benji.
我不知道该说什么好了  本杰
This is all so...
这一切实在太...
...romantic.
浪漫了
Or?
或者...
I know I may be way out of bounds here...
我知道  或者我做得太过火了
...but is there any chance you would take me back?
但我们还有机会在一起吗
Maybe.
或者可以...
Sweetie, this conversation is starting to
甜心  你们的对话
make me a little uncomfortable.
让我觉得有点不舒服了
Oh, God. I am so sorry, but--
天啊  我很抱歉  但...
I mean, there's so much history between us, you know?
我是说...我们之前有太多的过去了...
I'm sorry too.
我也觉得抱歉...
I love you.
我爱你
I love you too.
我也爱你
Okay, that's it, we are seeing other people.
好吧就这样  我们都可以找下家了
Gladys?
格拉达斯
For the third time this week.
这个星期的第三次了
Man, this does not get old.
天啊  真是常玩常新啊
You're mean!
你真可恶
Oh, don't be such a baby. Please.
不要这么孩子气啦